[
  {
    "question": "Which of these is not a concept associated with databases?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "View",
      "Table",
      "Index",
      "Desk"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Desk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is another way of saying a decimal numbering system?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Base99",
      "Base7",
      "Base10",
      "Base4"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Base10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an error condition that occurs during the execution of a Java program?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Discretion",
      "Calumniation",
      "Dissolution",
      "Exception"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Exception"
  },
  {
    "question": "As opposed to a variable, the value of which construct in a programming language never changes?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Fixed",
      "Stuck",
      "Static",
      "Constant"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Constant"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the acronym (pixel) refer to?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Photo element",
      "Picture information",
      "Picture element",
      "Phosphor location"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Picture element"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which programming language was created by James Gosling?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "awk",
      "JavaScript",
      "Java",
      "C"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Java"
  },
  {
    "question": "A (Universal Machine) was a concept designed by which computer scientist?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Alan Turing",
      "Claude Shannon",
      "John von Neumann",
      "Charles Babbage"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Alan Turing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language was once known as Oak, and then Green?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Java",
      "Pascal",
      "C#",
      "JavaScript"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Java"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these terms indicates that the OS does not have a requested (page)?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Page crash",
      "Interrupt",
      "Stack overflow",
      "Page fault"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Page fault"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JavaScript, how many times is a (do while) loop guaranteed to loop?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "1",
      "Infinitely until stopped",
      "Variable",
      "0"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JavaScript, which choice is the 5th element of the array named: score?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "*score[5]",
      "#score[4]",
      "score[4]",
      "score[5]"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "score[4]"
  },
  {
    "question": "A (query plan) is associated with which of these areas of computer science?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Assemblers",
      "Compilers",
      "Interpreters",
      "Databases"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Databases"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is a valid IP4 address format?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "10.10.255.0",
      "all of them",
      "192.168.1.1",
      "0.0.0.0"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "all of them"
  },
  {
    "question": "Files with .pl extension are associated with programming language?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Ruby",
      "Python",
      "Perl",
      "PHP"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Perl"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these programs is typically one of the first to be executed when a computer starts?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      "Memory Manager",
      "Bootloader",
      "Device Driver",
      "Task Scheduler"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": "Bootloader"
  }
]